Muhammad Mobeen

MERN Stack | Front-End | React | Software Developer

Summary

Experienced MERN Stack Developer with over 4 years of experience in Web and Mobile App Development. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction, talented at integrating novel design elements and interaction points to build new and exciting user experiences.

Experience

MERN Stack Developer

Nastech 2018-2020 Built and styled new mobilefriendly websites, transitioning legacy presentations to simultaneous easy-to-use versions.

React Native Developer

Nordstone 2020-2022

Built, tested, and deployed scalable, highly available, and modular Mobile Applications. Wrote clean, clear, and welltested code for 6+ projects.

Education

Army Public College

2018 - 2020

FSc in Computer Sceince

Igra University

2022 - continue

BSc in Software Engineering

Undergraduate

Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JSX, ES6, React JS, React Native, Redux, Bootstrap, Material UI, Axios, Firebase, Github, Jira, Mongo DB, Express JS, SQL, Angular, Figma, XD
- API integration
- · Proficient in Front-End Development
- Proficient in Web and Mobile App Development
- Development from scratch, following and mentaining documentation.

Contact



+92 308 3689852



mubeendevelop.web.app



mmmubeen761@gmail.com



Karachi, 75460 Pakistan